<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-CA"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://dancinglightstudios.ca/https://dancinglightstudios.ca/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://dancinglightstudios.ca/https://dancinglightstudios.ca/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en-CA" /><updated>2023-08-18T15:32:28+00:00</updated><id>https://dancinglightstudios.ca/https://dancinglightstudios.ca/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Dancing Light Studios</title><subtitle>Dancing Light Studios is poised to revolutionize the realms of education and entertainment through awe-inspiring AR, VR, and MR experiences. Our technology is driven by a passion to empower, engage, and enlighten. The canvas of possibilities is endless, and we’re painting it with pixels of progress. A new era beckons, and Dancing Light Studios is leading the way. Be part of the transformation – because everything is about to change.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Adaptive Ambition</title><link href="https://dancinglightstudios.ca/https://dancinglightstudios.ca/campfire/2023/adaptive-ambition/index.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Adaptive Ambition" /><published>2023-08-18T04:24:14+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-18T04:24:14+00:00</updated><id>https://dancinglightstudios.ca/https://dancinglightstudios.ca/campfire/2023/adaptive-ambition/adaptive-ambition</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://dancinglightstudios.ca/https://dancinglightstudios.ca/campfire/2023/adaptive-ambition/index.html"><![CDATA[<p>Adapting. Evolving. Growing. It’s what makes a morning jog turn into a marathon over time, a doodle transform into art, or a simple idea blossom into a revolutionary product. At Dancing Light, it’s the core of our value we fondly call Adaptive Ambition.</p>

<p>We’re a collective of dreamers, sure. But what sets our dreams apart? The drive to adapt them to the ever-changing realities of our world. We revel in the beauty of a challenge, not because it’s easy, but because it pushes us to learn, to pivot, and to find new horizons we hadn’t even imagined.</p>

<p>And while we’re ambitious about making a mark, we’re equally passionate about ensuring every member of our team feels the excitement of this journey. We believe in embracing change with open arms, learning from each twist and turn, and celebrating every small victory along the way.</p>

<p>So if you’ve ever found joy in the unexpected, or felt the thrill of adapting and evolving your ambitions, you’ll find a kindred spirit in us. We’re not just creating products, we’re nurturing an environment where every challenge is seen as an opportunity to grow.</p>

<p>And at the heart of it all? Our unwavering Adaptive Ambition. It’s not just a value; it’s a journey we invite you to join.</p>

<p><a href="/careers">Join Dancing Light Studios, check out our careers page</a></p>]]></content><author><name>Emily Mckee</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adapting. Evolving. Growing. It’s what makes a morning jog turn into a marathon over time, a doodle transform into art, or a simple idea blossom into a revolutionary product. At Dancing Light, it’s the core of our value we fondly call Adaptive Ambition.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Respectabilitude</title><link href="https://dancinglightstudios.ca/https://dancinglightstudios.ca/campfire/2023/respectabilitude/index.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Respectabilitude" /><published>2023-08-05T20:25:50+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-05T20:25:50+00:00</updated><id>https://dancinglightstudios.ca/https://dancinglightstudios.ca/campfire/2023/respectabilitude/respectabilitude</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://dancinglightstudios.ca/https://dancinglightstudios.ca/campfire/2023/respectabilitude/index.html"><![CDATA[<p><em>Respectabilatude</em> (noun): the quality or state of making those around you feel respected and valued; an attitude of genuine consideration and esteem for others.<br />
<br />
In a Sentence: “At Dancing Light Studios, respectabilatude is more than just a core value; it’s a practice that defines how team members engage with each other and their clients.”<br />
<br />
Thank you to Jesse Schell for putting a word on it. At Dancing Light, sincere respectabilatude is one of our core values. It is one of the key components we look for in team members and something we foster within the organization. It’s a philosophy that encourages us to approach each other’s ideas with curiosity and appreciation, to strive for what’s ‘technologically meaningful and impactful.’<br />
<br />
Respectabilatude allows us to break barriers in AR, VR, and projection-mapped location-based entertainment, not by creating a hierarchy of ideas but by celebrating the diversity of thought. From daily team collaborations to our extended relationships with clients, respectabilatude guides us to create an environment where diverse opinions are cherished, and everyone’s voice matters. It’s a living value that makes us more than just colleagues – we’re a community.</p>]]></content><author><name>Liam Knightley</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[*Respectabilatude* (noun): the quality or state of making those around you feel respected and valued; an attitude of genuine consideration and esteem for others.]]></summary></entry></feed>